var myQuestions = [
    {
        question: "1. What is the name of the killer in Scream?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Leatherface',
            b: 'Jason Vorhees',
            c: 'Michael Myers',
            d: 'Ghostface'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: "2. What is Sidney's last name?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Prescott',
            b: 'Weary',
            c: 'Strode',
            d: 'Wayne'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: "3. Who is the first victim in Scream?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Steve Orth',
            b: 'Casey Becker',
            c: 'Tatum Riley',
            d: 'Randy Meeks'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: "4. What is the killer's choice of weapon?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Machete',
            b: 'Knife',
            c: 'Gun',
            d: 'Chainsaw'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },

    {
        question: "5. What object falls out of Billy's pocket that makes Sidney suspicious?",
        answers: {
            a: 'A knife',
            b: 'A picture of her mom',
            c: 'A gun',
            d: 'A cell phone'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: "6. What is the name of Sidney's best friend?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Gale',
            b: 'Tatum',
            c: 'Stu',
            d: 'Randy'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "7. What is the killer's favourite question to ask his victims?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Do you want to die today?',
            b: 'Are you home alone?',
            c: 'What is your favourite scary movie?',
            d: 'Do you get scared easily?'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: "8. What is Gale's job?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Lawyer',
            b: 'Reporter',
            c: 'Nurse',
            d: 'Sheriff'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },

    {
        question: "9. What is the name of the fictional town the movie takes place?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Sunnydale',
            b: 'Haddonfield',
            c: 'Woodsboro',
            d: 'Crystal Lake'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: "10. Who is the final character to die in Scream?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Stu',
            b: 'Dewey',
            c: 'Kenny',
            d: 'Billy'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'd'
    }
];
